sup everyone timbers 1 2 3 4 5 p with a
very special video today now today's
Monday or as I like to call it chili dog
Monday cuz every Monday I have
chili dogs a mere for a true Sonic
humming around fan em around anyways
I've got a part of refried beans heating
up on the sub upstairs and and I
thought hey you know what while the
beans are heating up how about I have
our job our dog picture for my
so that's exactly what I'm going to do
I'll by the way those are my those are
these are my my official made Bobby and
Sonic Lego was over here in case you're
wondering this is Bobby and this is
Sonic if you're wanting why sock is
wearing handcuffs with let's just last
night let's just say last night before
beddy bye time I'm play with you for a
couple hours and they did some really
kinky if you know what I mean but
anyways it it does get drawn
now I'm going to need the black crown I
thought that I'm gonna drop bobbing
Sonic at the bitch oh I need the
brown for the santo the close one
got a color in the sand because
all features halves and MRI now other
off all bitches also have trait like
palm trees and so let's draw the
draw like a palm tree over over here in
the corner oh right us again good draw
some coconuts gonna need i
don't got a green crown oh well I guess
I'll guess I'll just this pumped you
don't need any legs up in this
so I'll just saw John Bobby there
I mean that's all everyone cares about
my well anyways I I need you pick up a
green crown from walmart
the US speaking of warm out I've got
this really funny sir what I find it's
kind of cool story actually just just a
couple days ago I went to warm out in
the in the inner child sections you buy
a sock on the ground DVD and and
while I was there I saw this kid
who couldn't have been like maybe six
seven years old anyway what happened was
in his hand was like he's a modern saw
toy and as you all know is that
that's just not right that's just not
cool so like I'm not even kidding I walk
up to that kid I asked hey would you get
that he said I was I'm buying this yeah
true silly I I punched a potion
it he cried like a and
but I didn't care I mean he his
parents came and asked what was going on
I'm not gonna lie I told them truth I
punch your kid well why are you having
him by and I'm not even King they
they stood up for me like like damn my
luck to be felt what parents by the kids
am a modern song to ensure that kid
uh-uh you don't raise a kid to do that
you buy that anyways the person the
employee had the they made the family
leave the store after I told them what
was going on because well the the people
in the store said I was Rio some
about the way of drawing waves
in the background sock is gonna be like
riding a surfboard anyways yeah I I wish
I brought my camera because it was so
cool I can't believe that happened
but yeah I did anyways that remind me of
another story actually this was like a
week or two a God or man but I was
buying a pizza and when I had to
the door somebody thought oh my God kids
would be five is that you now it took me
an Amir to wonder why how he realized I
was here only five and then well I uh I
had was horn like a Sonic Underground
plushie and as multiple no I'm like one
of the only soccer fans like a sadly in
existence right now and so he knew
right away I had to be tended five I
gave him an autograph and he he he gave
me a tip like he was the pizza
man I order pizza he came to my house
gave me a a tip after
realizing who I was the tip was about
like it was about like 14 bucks or some
like I couldn't believe that I just
said ok and then he went home I mean I
called them back because I realized they
accidentally gave me a pepperoni
when I ordered sausage and they came
back with like three more pieces of
three more like boxes of pizza not to
apologize but because they just wanted
to see me again you know I'm almost done
with this picture actually I'm
just I got you I Bobby saying I'm done
hmm gotta get that gotta get those
golden locks color dishes hmm I love
this I love this feeling John about
danik picture nothing makes me feel more
alive and is there
oh this is the goods look at that I will
give song a nose bleeding
because he's staring that's he's staring
at that ass right there Sonic
stock staring at data am I right thanks
for watching I gotta go eat my
chili dogs please